Oh my god
いっぱい 南に呪おう
力合わせて
ときめく 方へ急ごう
はじまりの合図
今こそ 空出の瞬間
光を上げたら
七色の風を切り冒険の海へ 傷だらけの旅だけど 大事なものがそこにある 銀紙ならいつだって 僕が守るから
大丈夫さ 前に進もう 太陽をいつも胸に 嵐が来たら肩組んで その先の光を見よう
夢のかけら集まれば 明日に向かう地図になる だから同じ旗のもと 願いをつかまえようよ
僕らはひとつわき
Come back! Quick! The sea's gonna swallow you up!
A sea anemone?
Why is a sea anemone coming out of a chimney?
Wait a second...
No wait! Not the reindeer too!
The reindeer too!
As she said Robin had a wish that couldn't come true as long as you were together
She surrendered her life to CP-9 in order to protect that very wish
in order to protect that very wish.
My wish is that all of the Straw Hat pirates, except me,
will be allowed to leave this island safely.
If I can have that, I'm willing to sacrifice myself
and everyone else in the world.
Robin, get off that train!
I don't care who you're up against, we'll help you!
Robin!
You're awesome, Pirate Lady!
Don't be a fool, girl.
You won't make it back in time.
You can see for yourself.
The wave's going to hit any second now.
Oh, man, there's no turning back now.
They're as good as dead.
Soro!
Hey!
You okay?
Can you hear me?
Chopper!
Oh!
This is it.
I can't go any further.
or something.
Where are you?
Well done.
Luffy!
Hey, why not?
You idiot! What the hell are you doing up there?
Nami, where are you? I can't see!
Okay, listen, listen, it's not my fault!
That pigeon guy sent me flying and I got stuck between these buildings so I can't move!
I'm trying, though!
Is this a joke to you? We don't have time for this!
Those guys from the government took Robin away and you weren't even there to help!
She did it all for us, you know! She's going to sacrifice herself!
The government was planning on attacking us, but Robin turned herself over to CP9 so we would be safe!
There's no place left in this world for me to go or return to.
I'm afraid you're wrong. This is the last time you'll ever see me.
She knew they would kill her, but she didn't care!
Then...
Robin was flying...
This whole time?
I'm glad...
Don't worry!
I won't let Robin die!
Check out the size of that thing!
Oh, man! The waves have never been that big before!
Hey! This is really bad, guys!
Run away, pirate lady!
You gotta get out of there!
You too, reindeer!
You're going to tear me in half!
You're really stuck!
How did you get in there in the first place?
Who cares?
What do we do?
That wave's going to hit any second now!
How the hell should I know?
Hold on. That's funny.
Hey, Chopper!
Are you carrying the content suit?
Huh? Your sword?
Yeah, I have one of them.
How on earth did you know that?
Well, I can tell with that one at least.
It's cursed.
Anyway, thanks for carrying it for me.
Here, quick!
Put it in my hand!
Run away!
Get higher ground!
Hurry!
It's all over!
They're not going to make it!
Pirate lady!
They'll get swept away for sure!
Aqua Laguna is here!
No!
Oh, no!
This is farewell.
I should have stayed at home!
This is too scary!
That wave's huge!
They're done for!
I should have stayed at home!
Whoa!
You should have stayed at home!
Whoa! That guy's out of control! He's blocking over buildings!
Tyler!
Stay back, Chopper!
One sort style... 36 caliber Phoenix!
This is bad! They're wrecking the town!
Nami! Let's go!
Holy crap!
Crumble! Jumping!
Just hold on to me!
They're forcing away!
Hey, look! They made it!
I think...
Yay! You did it!
They should be safe on the bridge!
Yeah, it's a big wave, but it's not that big!
You guys were amazing!
You gotta teach me that one!
Oh no! The tidal wave's still coming!
Destroy! Make it?
I don't know, man! All I can see is water!
Look! Over there!
It's falling!
Ah!
Crap!
Over there!
It's Pauly!
Crap!
Hurry!
We're not safe yet!
Run to shipbuilding island!
Run for it!
Rich is done for!
I've never seen anything like that!
The waves have never made it this far before!
I thought we'd be safe here!
Look!
The tide's ebbing again!
Of course it is!
This is just the beginning!
There's gonna be another wave like that!
And another after that one!
If we wanna live, we gotta get to higher ground!
夢見た僕らは間違いじゃないと信じて 荒く埋める海原を渡って行ける
誰よりも浮かんで 思いやりもあるけれど
もしも君がこの船を降りて 違う世界にいたとしても
最後にはきっと笑えるよ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Hey!
Let us borrow a ship!
A strong and fast one!
Not a chance!
Not in this storm!
I'd be sending you to an early grave!
I don't care!
Our friends are out there waiting for us!
Well, there is one way to get through Aqua Laguna.
If you're crazy enough to try it!
On the next, One Piece!
Another sea train?
Rocket Man charges forth!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
B